现在是时候向我们的新View中绘制内容来
Now, it's time to finish creating our new view
完成它了  我们在自定义View的
by drawing its contents. And, we do that within our
onDraw()方法中进行绘制  随着Android画布API的发展
Custom View's onDraw method. Now, the Android Canvas is pretty
它现在已经非常标准  它使用
standard as far as canvas API's go. It uses the
画家算法  这意味着你后绘制的新内容会
Painter's algorithm, meaning that each new thing you paint
覆盖之前的内容  Canvas和Paint类
will cover anything beneath it. The Canvas and Paint classes
提供很多的画笔和其它帮助来根据
offer a variety of brushes and helpers to draw and
颜色、图案、倾斜度和图片来绘制或者填充线条、方框、圆以及文字
fill lines, boxes, circles, and text with colors, patterns, gradients,
同时还提供在你绘制的时候进行移动、旋转和
and images, as well as offering the ability to move, rotate,
放大缩小画布的功能  我可以在这里
and scale the canvas while you draw. I could spend a lot
花很多时间来讲述到底怎么使用这些工具
of time here detailing exactly how to use each of these tools,
但是Android这方面的内容没有什么特殊的  而且它们在下面链接的文档中
but there's nothing unique to Android and it's covered really well on
有很详细的描述  我们可以这样来创建非常高级的
the documentation link below. It is possible though to create pretty advanced
界面  举个例子  比如我们先画一个圆
UIs this way. For example, for example, if we start by drawing
再添加第二个圆  然后你只需要
a circle and then add a second circle and then you just
绘制剩下的指南针  这是我预先准备的
need to finish drawing the rest of the compass. Here's an example
一个例子  你绘制的每一个View的细节
I prepared earlier. The specifics of what you draw are
都不尽相同  但是有一点相同的是
different for every view, but one thing that is consistent
你一直是在一个资源受限的设备上进行绘制的
is the resource constraint device you're drawing on. And that
onDraw()方法在每次屏幕刷新的时候都会被调用
the onDraw method be called every time the screen is
每秒钟会有很多次  这意味着
refreshed, potentially many times a second; that means any object
你在onDraw()方法中创建的任何对象  包括Paint对象
created here within your onDraw method, including things like Paint
都会频繁地被创建和销毁
objects, will be created and destroyed at an alarming frequency.
对象的创建和销毁在Android上的代价会很大
Object creation and destruction can be expensive on Android; potentially
大量垃圾回收可能会影响到界面的流畅性
effecting the smoothness of your UI, when garbage collection is initiated.
解决的方案就是将onDraw()循环中的对象
The solution? Move the scope of any object used within the
移到类中
onDraw loop, into the class scope. Go ahead and override the
去覆写你的新View中的onDraw()方法  来绘制新的控制界面
onDraw method within your new view and draw the new control.
其实  为什么不趁这个机会创建一个
In fact, why not take this opportunity to create a custom
同时显示风速、风向和阳光的自定义控制界面呢
control that can display the wind speed and direction fused within
完成以后  你就可以使用它的完全限定名
sunshine. Once you're done, you can add it to your layer
来把它添加到XML文件的布局层次中
using it it's full package name and class name in the XML
就像这样  运行一下  然后把你的新View的截图发到论坛中
like this. Run it and then post a screenshot of your new view into the forum.